Bardhi Grainca

Bardhi.grainca@hotmail.com - (389) 76-466-033 - Skopje, Macedonia

Experienced DevOps engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the Information technology and DevOps environments. Skilled in Database Administration, System Administration, Front-end Development, and Communication. Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from South East European University (SEEU).

WORK EXPERIENCE

ALTARO Aug 2020 – Present

DevOps Engineer

Skopje

- Windows Server 2012 R2, 2016, 2019
- Hyper-V Virtualization
- VMware Virtualization, ESXi, VCenter
- Database Management (MySQL)
- Highly Available Systems
- Altaro Products

Singular Nov 2019 – April 2020

DevOps Engineer

. Skopje

- Continuous integration (CI) continuous delivery (CD) with Jenkins
- Monitoring with Grafana (Percona), PRTG
- Troubleshooting application bugs
- Database management (MySQL)
- Log management (Graylog)
- Python Scripts, Bash Scripts

Stopanska Banka Main Branch

Jan 2019 - Nov 2019

System analyst

Skopje

- Collaborating with Business Analysts, Project Leads to resolve issues and ensuring solutions areviable
- Creating system guidelines and manuals for the organization
- Troubleshooting technical issues

SEAVUS Nov 2017 – Jan 2019

It and Operation Engineer

Skopje

- Diagnosing and solving customer software problems
- Provide technical assistance to the costumers like VOLVO, Rolls Royce, Ford, Tesla, and NATO.
- Test and reproduce reported issues and answer the technical questions, resolve customer problems.
- Aid concerning the use of computer hardware and software, including operating systems and application, databases, network, security.

EDUCATION

South East European University

2014 - 2017

Degree (BS), Majors (Computer Science)

Skopje

- Won 2 certificates on leadership and coding, also been part of NASA Space App Challenge
- I've won 1 place 2 years in a row in swimming competition

SKILLS & INTERESTS

- Skills: MySQL, SOAP, TOAD, LDAP, APACHE, .NET, SAP, Customer Service 1nd Level, 2nd Level;
- System Administrator, Windows Server 14, 16, Linux, VMware;
- Prototyping in XD, PSD, Al and converting them into Functional Webpages.
- HTML/CSS/Java Script, jQuery, UX/UI, Bootstrap, Python, BashScripting

Interests: Puns; Sleeping; Web-Design; Politics; Traveling;